(Mrs Latham:)Well, I must say, you make a
very persuasive case for it.
(Leonard:)Oh, good, good.
And I'm seriously
(Mrs Latham:)considering taking it
to the next level.
(Leonard:)Terrific. Great.
(Leonard:)What level is that?
(Leonard:)Okay, now you don't
remind me of my mom.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, so, eventually,
zombies are going to attack
(Sheldon:)the rehab facility
where Sandra Bullock is?
(Penny:)Yes, Sheldon. Keep watching.
(Sheldon:)You know, it's a shame, all that
work she's doing to get sober,
(Sheldon:)only to be torn apart
and eaten alive.
(Howard:)Hey. How was dinner?
(Leonard:)Swell. I need a drink.
(Leonard:)Do we have any alcohol?
(Sheldon:)No. But we have potatoes--
I could make you vodka.